Inventory of the American National Red Cross records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Commission for China (ARC China Famine Relief), 1920-1921
  - Peking Union Medical College, 1921
    Box/Folder 62: 1
  - District and divisions maps, 1921
    Box/Folder 62: 2
  - Medical and sanitary reports, 1921
    Box/Folder 62: 3-4
  - Director of Accounts Alfred E. Davies, reports, 1921
    Box/Folder 62: 5
  - Director Cecil M. Troxel, reports, 1920
    Box/Folder 62: 6
  - Report on number of men fed by ARC, 1921
    Box/Folder 62: 7
  - Personnel reports, 1921
    Box/Folder 62: 8
  - Reports on stores, Ping Yuan, 1921
    Box/Folder 62: 9-11
  - Chief Accountant William I. Lacy, reports, 1921 (Reel 85)
    Box/Folder 62: 12
  - Reports on activities, Tehchow, 1921
    Box/Folder 62: 13
  - Road construction project, reports, 1921
    Box/Folder 62: 14
  - Chair Alice C. Reed, correspondence re: children refugees, 1920
    Box/Folder 62: 15
  - China and Mongolia Export Co., Inc., 1920
    Box/Folder 62: 16
  - Chairman, Tehchow Famine Relief Society, A.D. Heininger, correspondence, 1921
    Box/Folder 62: 17
  - Chief Engineer Lawrence Impey, reports on construction work
    Box/Folder 62: 18
  - "Narrative of Trip to Tehchow," report by Lewis W. Cook, controller, ARC, National Headquarters, Washington, D.C., 1921
    Box/Folder 62: 19
  - Field manager Oliver J. Todd, reports regarding attack on engineer by the villagers, 1921
    Box/Folder 62: 20
  - Reports on equipment, 1921
    Box/Folder 62: 21
  - Chief of commissary Paul MacEachron, reports, 1921
    Box/Folder 62: 22
  - Minutes of Field staff meeting, February 21, 1921
    Box/Folder 62: 23
  - Supplies of grain, beans, coal, wood, and rice bran, reports, 1921
    Box/Folder 62: 24
  - Land purchase for roads, 1921
    Box/Folder 62: 25-26
  - Field manager Oliver J. Todd, completion reports, 1921
    Box/Folder 62: 27-29
  - Superintendent of relief and commissary F.F. Tucker, reports, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 62: 30-32
  - Chief engineer, highway construction, K.C. Weedin, reports, 1920
    Box/Folder 62: 33
  - Henry B. Leitzel, district missionary, correspondence, 1921
    Box/Folder 62: 34
  - Joseph Bailie, correspondence, 1921
    Box/Folder 62: 35
  - Correspondence, telegrams, summarized, 1921
    Box/Folder 62: 36
  - Assistant chief of commissary Richard B. Irving, correspondence, 1921
    Box/Folder 63: 1
  - Government, correspondence, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 63: 2
  - Construction equipment, reports, 1921
    Box/Folder 63: 3
  - Standard Oil Company of New York, 1921
    Box/Folder 63: 4
  - Supplies, Kai-Mun Trading Company, 1921
    Box/Folder 63: 5
  - Supplies, Purchasing of food, correspondence, reports, 1921
    Box/Folder 63: 6-13
  - Supplies, Construction materials and equipment, 1921
    Box/Folder 63: 14
  - Clippings from Chinese newspapers in English, 1920-1921 (Reel 86)
    Box/Folder 63: 15-18
  - Index to files, 1921
    Box/Folder 64: 1
  - Appeals, undated
    Box/Folder 64: 2
  - Accounts, classification and description, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 64: 3
  - American Consular Service, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 64: 4-5
  - American Legation, Peking, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 64: 6-7
  - Appreciation from Chinese officials, 1920
    Box/Folder 64: 8
  - John Earl Baker, Director ARC, Appointment as director of China Famine Relief, 1920
    Box/Folder 64: 9
  - John Earl Baker, Director ARC, Correspondence, reports, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 64: 10
  - John Earl Baker, Director ARC, "Broad Tires the Next Stabs towards Good Roads," by J.E. Baker, report, undated
    Box/Folder 64: 11
  - John Earl Baker, Director ARC, Correspondence, reports to National Headquarters, Washington, D.C., 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 64: 12-13
  - British Legation, Peking, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 64: 14
  - British-American Tobacco Company, Ltd., 1921
    Box/Folder 64: 15
  - Central Purchasing Agency, 1921
    Box/Folder 64: 16
  - Chihli Field, 1920-1921
    - Hantan, reports, 1920-1921
      Box/Folder 64: 17-21
    - Paotingfu, reports, 1920-1921
      Box/Folder 64: 22-24
    - Peking, reports, 1921
      Box/Folder 64: 25
    - Tamingfu, correspondence, 1921
      Box/Folder 64: 26
    - Tientsin cashier's daily gold statements, 1921 (Reel 87)
      Box/Folder 64: 27
    - Tientsin reports, 1920-1921
      Box/Folder 64: 28
  - Chief engineer Lawrence Impey, reports, 1921
    Box/Folder 64: 29
  - Tungchow-Tientsin Highway, reports, 1921
    Box/Folder 64: 30
  - Clippings from Chinese newspapers in English, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 64: 31-32
  - Director of accounts Alfred Davies, reports to National Headquarters Washington, D.C., 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 65: 1-2
  - Manager and director of civilian relief, National Headquarters Washington, D.C., Emmet W. White, correspondence, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 65: 3
  - The National Committee of the Young Men's Christian Associations of China, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 65: 4
  - National Headquarters Washington, D.C., correspondence, reports, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 65: 5
  - Thomas H. Wiggin, Grand Canal Improvement Board, reports, 1920
    Box/Folder 65: 6
  - Building wells, reports, 1921
    Box/Folder 65: 7
  - United States Forces, China Expedition, correspondence, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 65: 8
  - Tientsin-Pukow Line, Chinese Government Railways, Traffic Department, 1921
    Box/Folder 65: 9
  - Transportation, reports, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 65: 10-11
  - Report of the China Famine Relief American Red Cross, October 1920--September 1921, illustrated with photographs (Reel 88)
    Box/Folder 65: 12
  - Grain Yard, Paoting Fu, glass plate negative, undated
    Box/Folder 65: 13
  - Chinese college students in relief work, 1921
    Box/Folder 65: 14
  - Chinese Government Telephone Administration, 1920
    Box/Folder 65: 15
  - Chinese governors and ministers, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 65: 16
  - Chung Hsing Coal Mining Co., Ltd., 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 65: 17
  - Peking-Mukden Railway, Chinese Government Railways, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 65: 18
  - Chinese Telegraph Administration, 1921
    Box/Folder 65: 19-20
  - Commissary Department, letters, instructions, forms, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 65: 21-22
  - Ministry of Communications, correspondence, reports, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 65: 23-24
  - Carl Crow Inc.--Advertising and Merchandising Service, 1921 (Reel 89)
    Box/Folder 66: 1
  - American Consular Service, Dairen, Manchuria, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 66: 2
  - Director of accounts Alfred Davies, correspondence, reports, 1921
    Box/Folder 66: 3-7
  - North China Motor Club, 1921
    Box/Folder 66: 8
  - Engineering Department, reports, 1921
    Box/Folder 66: 9-14
  - Asia Banking Corporation, exchange rates, 1921
    Box/Folder 66: 15
  - Asia Banking Corporation, exchange rates, 1921 (Reel 90)
    Box/Folder 66: 16-17
  - Famine area, statistics, undated
    Box/Folder 66: 18
  - "15th Infantry Men,", 1921
    Box/Folder 66: 19
  - Grain merchants, reports, Dairen, Manchuria, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 66: 20-21
  - Financial reports, 1921
    Box/Folder 66: 22-23
  - Hawaiian Chapter, Honolulu, correspondence, 1921
    Box/Folder 66: 24
  - Honan Field, reports, 1921
    Box/Folder 66: 25
  - Hongkong and Shanghai Banking Corporation, 1921
    Box/Folder 66: 26
  - Identification tags for famine relief workers, 1921
    Box/Folder 66: 27
  - Interpreters for ARC, correspondence, 1921
    Box/Folder 66: 28
  - Japan Chapter, reports on activities, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 67: 1
  - Kailan Mining Administration, regulations, reports, 1921
    Box/Folder 67: 2
  - Assistant engineer Theodore Kelly--Dismissal, reports, 1921
    Box/Folder 67: 3
  - L.H. Lancaster, American Presbyterian Mission, correspondence, 1921
    Box/Folder 67: 4
  - Miscellany, correspondence, 1921
    Box/Folder 67: 5-6
  - Maps of relief areas (Reel 91)
    Box/Folder 67: 7
  - Medical work, 1921
    Box/Folder 67: 8
  - Reports on passes, correspondence, 1921
    Box/Folder 67: 9
  - Reports on passes, passes on the railroads, customs, personnel, 1921
    Box/Folder 67: 10-13
  - Reports on passes, telegraph passes, 1921
    Box/Folder 67: 14
  - Permanent foundations, reports, 1921
    Box/Folder 67: 15-16
  - Personnel files, 1921
    Box/Folder 67: 17-20
  - Personnel files, 1921 (Reel 92)
    Box/Folder 67: 21-23
  - Donations from Philippines, 1921
    Box/Folder 67: 24
  - Prevention of plague and typhus, 1921
    Box/Folder 67: 25
  - Millard's Review of the Far East, vol. XV, no. 3, December 18, 1920
    Box/Folder 67: 26
  - Press releases, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 67: 27-28
- Commission for Czechoslovakia, 1919-1922
  - League of Red Cross Societies, reports, 1919-1921
    Box/Folder 68: 1
  - Reports on activities, 1920-1922
    Box/Folder 68: 2
  - Reports on activities, 1920-1922 (Reel 93)
    Box/Folder 68: 3-12
  - Prisoners and refugees of war, 1921
    Box/Folder 68: 13
  - Russian prisoners of war, 1919
    Box/Folder 68: 14
  - Personnel, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 68: 15
  - Personnel, 1920-1921 (Reel 93 A)
    Box/Folder 68: 16
  - Appreciation letters, 1922
    Box/Folder 68: 17-18
  - Liquidation reports, 1921-1922
    Box/Folder 68: 19
  - Miscellany reports, 1920-1922
    Box/Folder 68: 20
  - Financial reports, 1920-1922
    Box/Folder 68: 21-22
  - Supplies, 1920
    Box/Folder 69: 1
  - Child health, 1920-1922
    Box/Folder 69: 2-4
  - Publicity, 1921-1922
    Box/Folder 69: 5-6
  - Appeals, 1920-1922 (Reel 94)
    Box/Folder 69: 7-8
  - Letters of appreciation, 1919-1922
    Box/Folder 69: 9
  - Program, 1921-1922
    Box/Folder 69: 10-11
  - Measures for combating typhus in Czechoslovakia, report to Dr. Alice Masaryk, President of Czechoslovak Red Cross, Prague, Department of Sanitation, Geneva, Switzerland, July 22, 1920
    Box/Folder 69: 12
  - Report on Dr. Pitt's tour through Slovakia and Ruthenia, July 2-August 5, 1920
    Box/Folder 69: 13
  - ARC, Bureau of Transportation, correspondence, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 69: 14
  - Civilian relief, 1920-1922
    Box/Folder 69: 15
  - Medical work, 1920-1922
    Box/Folder 69: 16
  - School for nurses, 1920-1922
    Box/Folder 69: 17-18
  - Personnel, 1922
    Box/Folder 69: 19
- Commission for France, 1915-1922
  See also Commission for Switzerland/Children's photographs and thank you letters, microfilm reels 116-117
  - Specification of executive and other personnel in French service, undated (Reel 95)
    Box/Folder 70: 1
  - Captain H.M. Reed, ARC, reports, 1918
    Box/Folder 70: 2-3
  - Index to files, 1917-1920
    Box/Folder 70: 4
  - Accueil Franco-Américain aux Réfugiés Belges et Français, 1917
    Box/Folder 70: 5
  - Accounting classification of the ARC in France, Definitions of, undated
    Box/Folder 70: 6
  - L'Aide Immédiate aux Agriculteurs des Régions Dévastées pour la Reconstitution du Matériel Agricole, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 70: 7
  - L'Aiguille Française Ventaire National, 1917
    Box/Folder 70: 8
  - "De l'Aisne," report, December 1920
    Box/Folder 70: 9. Includes map of Department de l'Aisne
  - Ambulances, reports, clippings, 1917
    Box/Folder 70: 10
  - Major-General John J. Pershing, reports, 1917-1919
    Box/Folder 70: 11
  - Maisons Américaines de Convalescence, 1919
    Box/Folder 70: 12
  - American Embassy, 1920
    Box/Folder 70: 13
  - American Expeditionary Forces, correspondence, reports, 1917-1920
    Box/Folder 70: 14-17
  - "The American Expeditionary Forces and the American Red Cross," by Colonel Olds, memorandum, 1918
    Box/Folder 70: 18
  - American Expeditionary Forces, Liaison officer of ARC, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 70: 19
  - American Expeditionary Forces, Massachusetts men in France, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 70: 20
  - American Expeditionary Forces, Orders, general and special, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 70: 21
  - American Expeditionary Forces, Division of Orthopedic Surgery, 1917
    Box/Folder 70: 22
  - Newspapers and magazines distribution, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 70: 23
  - American Fund for French Wounded, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 70: 24-26
  - American Girls Aid for the Collection of Clothing for Victims of the European War in France, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 70: 27
  - Red Cross Bulletin, Paris, 1918-1919 (Reel 96)
    Box/Folder 70: 28-29
  - Departmental history, reports, 1919
    Box/Folder 71: 1-2
  - Decorations, Richelieu medal, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 71: 3
  - Memorandum re relations of Red Cross, YMCA and similar societies to the sanitary service, U.S. Army, 1918
    Box/Folder 71: 4
  - Personnel--Emergency evacuation, instructions, correspondence, 1918
    Box/Folder 71: 5
  - Le Messager, French bulletin, 1917-1919
    Box/Folder 71: 6
  - ARC, map of Paris, undated
    Box/Folder 71: 7
  - Status of ARC in France, 1917-1919
    Box/Folder 71: 8-9
  - Narrative account of ARC activities, 1917-1919
    Box/Folder 71: 10
  - Acte de Constitution de la Croix-Rouge Américaine et Actes d'Amendements, 1918
    Box/Folder 71: 11
  - Major Murphy Grayson, report, 1917
    Box/Folder 71: 12
  - Description of ARC organization in France, 1918
    Box/Folder 71: 13
  - American Relief Warehouse Corporation, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 71: 14
  - ARC Commission--Organization for work in Europe, 1917 (Reel 97)
    Box/Folder 71: 15
  - Correspondence, 1918
    Box/Folder 71: 16
  - "Note sur la Croix-Rouge Américaine,", 1918
    Box/Folder 71: 17
  - American Relief Clearing House, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 71: 18
  - The American Social Hygiene Association, 1919
    Box/Folder 71: 19
  - American Women's Hospital, 1919
    Box/Folder 71: 20
  - Appreciations, 1917-1922
    Box/Folder 71: 21-28
  - Appreciations, 1917-1922
    Box/Folder 72: 1-2
  - Arras (Pas-de-Calais) devastated sector, map, undated
    Box/Folder 72: 3
  - Artificial limbs, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 72: 4
  - Westchester County Chapter, 1917
    Box/Folder 72: 5
  - Automobile transportation in France, reports, correspondence, photographs, 1917-1922
    Box/Folder 72: 6
  - Automobile transportation in France, reports, correspondence, photographs, 1917-1922 (Reel 98)
    Box/Folder 72: 7
  - Expenses for operating port offices of the Bureau of Transportation, 1918
    Box/Folder 72: 8
  - Boy Scouts Français, 1921
    Box/Folder 72: 9
  - Bureau de Bienfaisance, 1920
    Box/Folder 72: 10
  - Reports of the activities at Brest, 1919
    Box/Folder 72: 11
  - Buffalo War Relief Committee, 1917
    Box/Folder 72: 12
  - Cable Bureau, Department of Civil Affairs, 1919
    Box/Folder 72: 13
  - Cambrai Nord, Sous-Préfecture, 1921
    Box/Folder 72: 14
  - Cambrai warehouse reports, 1920
    Box/Folder 72 :15
  - Cannes, reports of activities, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 72: 16
  - Canteens at various points, reports, instructions, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 72: 17-18
  - Laura Belle Crandall, Red Cross Service, oversees records, 1919
    Box/Folder 72: 19-23. Includes travel documents, certificate, clippings, linens, and buttons from uniform
  - Candry, reports of activities, 1921
    Box/Folder 72: 24
  - Bureau of Canteens, instructions, reports, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 72: 25
  - Service for American relatives visiting cemeteries, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 72: 26-28
  - Centre de Rapatriement, 1920 (Reel 99)
    Box/Folder 73: 1
  - Cercle Feillet (Foyer de la Jeune Fille), 1920
    Box/Folder 73: 2
  - Supplies for children, Cernay, 1921
    Box/Folder 73: 3
  - Chaplains at hospitals, instructions, 1918
    Box/Folder 73: 4
  - Château Dauzac, par Macau, Gironde, 1920
    Box/Folder 73: 5
  - Child health, Reims, 1921-1922
    Box/Folder 73: 6-7
  - Child welfare, 1919-1922
    Box/Folder 73: 8-9
  - Transportation of children to the United States, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 73: 10
  - Children's Bureau, Department of Civil Affairs, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 73: 11
  - Special Christmas Fund, 1918-1920
    Box/Folder 73: 12
  - Department of Civil Affairs, reports, 1917-1921
    Box/Folder 73: 13-16
  - Bureau of Emergency Relief, reports, 1918-1921
    Box/Folder 73: 17-18
  - Department of Claims and Adjustments, report, June 1919
    Box/Folder 73: 19
  - Garments for refugees, 1917-1919
    Box/Folder 73: 20
  - Coal supplies, correspondence, 1919
    Box/Folder 73: 21
  - College Units, reports on the activities, 1918-1919 (Reel 100)
    Box/Folder 73: 22-23. Also includes documentation on relief work in China, 1920-1921
  - Comité Américain pour les Régions Dévastées de la France, 1918-1920
    Box/Folder 73: 24
  - Comité Franco-Américain pour la Protection des Enfants de la Frontière, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 73: 25
  - Comité Permanent Interallié, 1920
    Box/Folder 74: 1
  - Emergency canteen at Compiègne, 1918
    Box/Folder 74: 2
  - Paris-Washington, D.C., correspondence, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 74: 3-8
  - Conseil Général Fund, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 74: 9
  - Department of Engineering and Construction, 1917
    Box/Folder 74: 10
  - Morning conferences held in Colonel Olds' Office, minutes, notes, 1920 (Reel 101)
    Box/Folder 74: 11-13
  - Operation by ARC of convalescent home no. 11 for women, general instruction, 1919
    Box/Folder 74: 14
  - Cooperating agencies, lists, Department of Civil Affairs, 1919
    Box/Folder 74: 15
  - Cost of living in France, report by director of foreign accounts Nelson Mills, 1922
    Box/Folder 74: 16
  - Reeducation Center for French mutilés, Farm Courbat, Le Liège, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 74: 17
  - Croix-Rouge Française, 1917-1919
    Box/Folder 74: 18-19
  - Daily Bulletin issued by Publicity Department, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 74: 20-22
  - Department of Public Information, 1919-1920 (Reel 102)
    Box/Folder 75: 1
  - Chairman Henry P. Davison, correspondence, Washington, D.C., 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 75: 2
  - U.S. Food Administration--Animal situation in France, reports, 1918
    Box/Folder 75: 3
  - Decoration, Legion of Honor, 1919
    Box/Folder 75: 4
  - Operation of dispensaries, reports, 1919-1921
    Box/Folder 75: 5-10
  - Donations, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 75: 11-14
  - Ligue pour l'Education en Plein Air, 1921
    Box/Folder 75: 15
  - L'Enfant au Grand Air, 1921
    Box/Folder 75: 16
  - Ecole de Service Social, 1921
    Box/Folder 75: 17
  - Les Enfants Heureux, 1921
    Box/Folder 75: 18
  - Fatherless children of France, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 75: 19
  - Fichier Central d'Assistance et d'Aide Sociale, 1918
    Box/Folder 75: 20
  - Advice of Finance Committee action, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 75: 21-25
  - Minutes of Finance Committee, 1917-1919
    Box/Folder 75: 26-27
  - Minutes of Finance Committee, 1917-1919 (Reel 103)
    Box/Folder 76: 1-3
  - Fondation Franco-Américaine de Lyon, 1919
    Box/Folder 76: 4
  - Food for France Fund, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 76: 5
  - Department of Foreign Accounts, minutes, 1920
    Box/Folder 76: 6
  - Foyer Cambraisien, Cambrai, 1920
    Box/Folder 76: 7
  - Foyer des Alliés, 1919
    Box/Folder 76: 8
  - Foyer du Soldat, 1920
    Box/Folder 76: 9
  - Foyer des Mobilisés Venus de l'Amérique Latine, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 76: 10
  - La Renaissance des Foyers en Alsace, 1918
    Box/Folder 76: 11
  - Foyers du Soldat pour l'Armée d'Orient, 1918
    Box/Folder 76: 12
  - Secours Franco-Américain pour la France Dévastée, 1920
    Box/Folder 76: 13
  - Ministère de la Guerre, 1915-1918
    Box/Folder 76: 14-15
  - Ministères, correspondence, 1918
    Box/Folder 76: 16-17
  - Les Amis de la France, 1919
    Box/Folder 76: 18
  - General relief, reports, 1917-1922
    Box/Folder 76: 19-20
  - General relief, reports, 1917-1922 (Reel 104)
    Box/Folder 76: 21-26
  - General relief, reports, 1917-1922 (Reel 105)
    Box/Folder 77: 1-4
  - Home service, reports, correspondence, 1918-1920
    Box/Folder 77 :5-9
  - Hospitals, 1916-1921
    - General, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 77: 10-11
    - Ambulance Committee, minutes, 1916-1917
      Box/Folder 77: 12-13
    - American Hospital of Paris, 1917-1919 (Reel 106)
      Box/Folder 77: 14-15
    - Allies Anglo-French Hospital, Annel, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 77: 16-17
    - Base hospital no. 41, 1918
      Box/Folder 77: 18
    - Base hospital no. 82, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 77: 19
    - Belgian hospitals, 19161-1918
      Box/Folder 78: 1-2
    - American Children's Hospital at Evian, 1917-1918
      Box/Folder 78: 3
    - French hospitals, general instructions, 1918
      Box/Folder 78: 4
    - Military hospitals, Meuse, 1919
      Box/Folder 78: 5
    - French military hospital, Talence, 1920
      Box/Folder 78: 6
    - Serbian hospital at Malabry, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 78: 7-8
    - List of French sanitary formations to which the department of French hospitals of the ARC has sent supplies from, July 1917 to January 1919
      Box/Folder 78: 9-10
    - ARC military hospitals, 1917-1920 (Reel 107)
      Box/Folder 78: 11-18
    - ARC hospital for the civil population, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 78: 19
    - Hertford British hospital, 1920
      Box/Folder 78: 20
    - L'Hôpital Cochin, Paris, 1919
      Box/Folder 78: 21
    - L'Hôpital Militaire de Vaugirard, 1919-1921
      Box/Folder 78: 22
    - L'Hôpital at Aubervilliers, 1919
      Box/Folder 78: 23
    - Hospice Civil de Brest, 1920
      Box/Folder 78: 24
    - The Red Cross on the Front line in the Great Battle of 1918, by Edward Eyre Hunt, Paris
      Box/Folder 78: 25
    - Infirmerie du 34ème Régiment d'Aviation, 1921
      Box/Folder 78: 26
  - Inspection trips, 1919
    Box/Folder 78: 27
  - Home service, 1919
    Box/Folder 78: 28
  - Italian Government bills, 1920-1922
    Box/Folder 78: 29
  - Future of Junior ARC in Europe, program, 1921
    Box/Folder 78: 30
  - La Croix-Rouge Américaine, by Paul U. Kellogg, Paris, undated (Reel 108)
    Box/Folder 79: 1
  - Le Bronze Marc, 1920
    Box/Folder 79: 2
  - Jurisdictions of the French courts over the ARC, 1905-1920
    Box/Folder 79: 3-8
  - Bureau of the Liberated Zone, reports, summary, 1917-1920
    Box/Folder 79: 9
  - Laneville clinics, reports, 1918
    Box/Folder 79: 10
  - List showing ARC activities in the alphabetical order of towns with their locations according to geographic map sections, (A), undated
    Box/Folder 79: 11
  - List showing ARC activities (only) classified by symbols, to be used in connection with index shown on geographic maps, (B), undated
    Box/Folder 79: 12
  - Liquidations, reports, 1918-1922
    Box/Folder 79: 13-17
  - Mme Marchand, correspondence, report, 1920
    Box/Folder 79: 18
  - Maps of warehouse districts, 1918
    Box/Folder 79: 19
  - Assistance to immigrants in Marseille, 1919-1921
    Box/Folder 79: 20
  - From French "Mascots" to their American "Godfathers," letters from French war orphans "adopted" by members of the American Expeditionary Forces to their soldier friends, ARC, Paris, 1919
    Box/Folder 79: 21
  - Maternity hospital, Montdidier, 1919-1921
    Box/Folder 79: 22
  - Medical Advisory Committee, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 79: 23
  - Medical Research Committee, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 79: 24
  - Medical relief report, 1919
    Box/Folder 79: 25
  - Membership in ARC, foreign societies, 1918
    Box/Folder 79: 26
  - Medical work, reports, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 79: 27
  - Methodist Committee, 1919
    Box/Folder 79: 28
  - Military courtesy and rules, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 79: 29
  - Militarization of ARC, 1917
    Box/Folder 79: 30
  - Military grade for women physicians, 1917 (Reel 109)
    Box/Folder 80: 1
  - Department of Military Affairs, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 80: 2
  - Military relief, 1919-1921
    Box/Folder 80: 3-4
  - Miscellany, 1919
    Box/Folder 80: 5
  - Major Murphy Grayson, correspondence, reports, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 80: 6
  - National Surgical Dressing Committee, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 80: 7
  - Nursing service, 1917-1919
    Box/Folder 80: 8-9
  - Oeuvre de la Paroisse de l'Aisne, 1921
    Box/Folder 80: 10